{
    "javascriptCurriculumDUMP": {
      "subtopics": [
        {
          "id": "1",
          "title": "Comments and Printing",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "1",
              "question": "To assign the value 20 to a variable named age, you write var ______.",
              "answer": "age=20"
            },
            {
                "id": "2",
                "question": "To create a string variable called city with the value \"Paris\", you write var ______.",
                "answer": "city=\"Paris\""
            },
            {
                "id": "3",
                "question": " To declare a float variable price with the value 19.99, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "price=19.99"
            },
            {
                "id": "4",
                "question": "To print the value of a variable name, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "is_student=True"
            },
            {
                "id": "5",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "print(name)"
            },
            {
                "id": "6",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "is_present"
            },
            {
                "id": "7",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "count=0"
            },
            {
                "id": "8",
                "question": "To declare an integer variable count and set it to zero, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "total=x+5"
            },
            {
                "id": "9",
                "question": "To create a variable name that stores the string \"Alice\", you write var ______.",
                "answer": "name=\"Alice\""
            },
            {
                "id": "10",
                "question": "To declare an integer variable tasks and set it to 7, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "tasks=7"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2",
          "title": "Variables & Data Types",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "1",
              "question": "To assign the value 20 to a variable named age, you write var ______.",
              "answer": "age=20"
            },
            {
                "id": "2",
                "question": "To create a string variable called city with the value \"Paris\", you write var ______.",
                "answer": "city=\"Paris\""
            },
            {
                "id": "3",
                "question": " To declare a float variable price with the value 19.99, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "price=19.99"
            },
            {
                "id": "4",
                "question": "To print the value of a variable name, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "is_student=True"
            },
            {
                "id": "5",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "print(name)"
            },
            {
                "id": "6",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "is_present"
            },
            {
                "id": "7",
                "question": "",
                "answer": "count=0"
            },
            {
                "id": "8",
                "question": "To declare an integer variable count and set it to zero, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "total=x+5"
            },
            {
                "id": "9",
                "question": "To create a variable name that stores the string \"Alice\", you write var ______.",
                "answer": "name=\"Alice\""
            },
            {
                "id": "10",
                "question": "To declare an integer variable tasks and set it to 7, you write var ______.",
                "answer": "tasks=7"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  }